The cards laid out for show
Star shine is so bright
Watch the secrets unfold
There's magic in her hands
Whisper what the future holds
Dance to the mystery
Yeah, yeah, yeah
So let the tarot move
We are Kangol
Hi guys
Uh, let me put this on the floor. Yeah, I thought I'd stop by a little
A little bit more hurrah tonight and I do have a piece of like I think cheesecake factory chocolate mousse cheesecake
My neighbors gave me for my birthday, which is quite a while ago
I'm just kind of move fast guys. Look, I already have my old head blown back on. I was having technical difficulties all night with
Stuff but yeah, I wanted to talk to you guys like actually I can't like really I need to word these glasses are a little bit strong
I mean, it's like there's a completely blurry unless I'm like reading it with them
So I'm gonna take them off for a minute because my eyes are a little bit sore. How are you doing?
Okay, and now it is very hard to see this the screen again. Let me so
This is what they call a catch 22 guys. Let me just find my glasses. Let me see
Where's my other ones?
I'm glad that like Amazon does have pretty easy return policy. I just don't see my other glasses. Where are they? Okay, are they here?
Yes, no, it's not them. Wow. Oh guys, hold on a second. Hello
Hi, babe
It's really weird since I clean my like place. It's like everything is like so
So organized and clean and like
Nice, it's really here. I think these are that what he's done
No
Well
Let's have to do it the ones I got
Okay, I don't know where I put the other ones
All this you have to read the chat more carefully, right? Okay?
Guys, we got some hey tree frog. How are you two problems a member and
Yes, we got two brothers a member awesome
guys, I just went through and I think I took about 50 60 hours of
Stuff that was just on the members. I put it back on public. I put it under
You know, I monetized it I
Think it is good to have like some more of these hours out
Yeah, there are a lot of nice shows that were copyright claims and stuff
As well as other you know unfortunate things happen, but I think I got the hang of this YouTube stuff
I think I went through kind of like a negative situation, but
Wow, it could have been so much worse and
I'm lucky to still be here
I'm actually successful on YouTube and people were like oh, it's impossible. You're never you're never gonna be anything on YouTube
Nobody nobody makes anything
I didn't go in thinking that out. I came in thinking hey, I got a business. I have a you know a talent I can use I can you know
offered terror readings and I think it's
No, I think it's a it's a
Respectable and you know, I see they had you know fair hero readers were once considered like
You know, the male ones were certainly considered gay, especially males that were into some of the divination and stuff like that.
In Norway, it's called theater, S-E-I-D-R. It means shaking.
And Odin actually was an expert at it, but so was Freya, right?
and it was considered like a kind of womanly thing,
but Odin couldn't get away with anything, right?
But, yeah, but he was one of the,
and I don't know if the Loki was ever, ever did it,
but yeah, the Norse did play with the gender roles a little bit,
you know, and we can still have kind of interesting stuff
going on with like the white supremacy and stuff,
which is not anything I support.
Hi, everybody.
So yeah, now I need to put my glasses on again.
I just see the screen I need to,
but I need to get kind of close,
and then it looks like really weird.
Hi, hey Jesus Christ. How are you guys doing?
But I've been having so I've been on tiktok to you. It's I've been like, you know, I didn't want to like
You know, okay, I've been on YouTube for like
Thousands and thousands and thousands of hours like thousands of hours like you know, it's just like it's every day this year
you know like half my day like I'm just like
put so much into it and
I don't want to get like too like old. I just know I notice like I go through ups and downs on YouTube
People like me one day. They don't like me the next day. I'm controversial
so many guys so many things have been said about me. It's like
Any normal person would not be able to like
Yeah, it takes a certain person like me that's able to like take all this criticism and just like is used to it all his life, right?
but
Wow, I kind of pretty much the worst stuff said about me that I mean I see other people get it bad, too
And I know and some people's people been canceled and have been destroyed or stuff
But for for being me being a nice person and I think I'm a nice person. I
Sure get a lot of shit. I get a lot of shit from people
You know, I'm sensitive too a little sensitive about it. Oh shit, I do have a nice amount of
of a THC left in here.
Well, there's a sense of about it
because I really do love people.
I even like people that don't like me.
I think there's reasons people,
because one doesn't like me, they don't know me probably.
It's like they don't know me.
Because anybody that you really get to know,
unless they're just like a full first person,
it's like there's some good quality in everybody.
Maybe I'm not perfect. I'm not like the best person in the world
Never said I was never I've always been like happy to be kind of you know scapegoated
It's called called the devil and stuff capricorns are usually called the devil you went to bought you went to Bobby's
See, yeah capricorns are known as a devil and you know devil's not necessarily very flattering things sometimes
Sometimes it's more popular in some circles other circles, right? It's like I don't really believe in like
Support like it's celebrating evil. That's when it really comes down to a Satan is them as practice in America
Is there kind of a negative thing or it's like even if it's not no sacrificing animals and stuff like that
Which is terrible. No one should be doing it
Even if it's not that it's just like about
Even seeing human beings as animals and I just got like there's a really mean that mean a thing along with it
You know, it's like
And then they also, I noticed a lot of narcissism in it too.
There's a lot of narcissism,
like this is the epidemic narcissism in the satanic search.
They think they're gods and everyone else is an animal.
And it's not just a fateness,
it goes into different secret societies too.
I mean, if you look at like these pictures
of some of these secret society people
and just how they have bumper stickers and rings
and like a little, they have to have a million,
like little,
Honor we're honors and recognitions and this is this like mr. Big Pipe's thing
Oh, I'm two times streamer the month according to Alex, you know, and Alex is a great person
I like her stream of the month, but she doesn't even like she's not even broadcasting right now
It's like what is what does it mean the upper of Alex my Alex mayors makes you two times shimmer of the month and mr.
Big pipes doesn't mean anything. Okay. I can be called to have a shimmer of the month by
Jamie's cowboys and beat his kiddies and a million other people and it doesn't mean shit, right? Hey, God
Gaudi
So yeah, I mean it's like can you can say whatever you want about that Gaudi
It's like I don't know how how much into the Satanism and you are if you are or not all
It is kind of like a along the line to declare yourself God
And that's fine if you do as they I don't know how serious you really do take it
Personally, it's like, yeah, we all have, it's like I'm pantheist or it's like, you know, I believe that everything is pantheist, am I pantheist?
Yeah, I believe everything is pantheist. I mean, it's like we're all part of something, we're all part of something, like a whole, right?
We're all, not a H-O-L-E, not a H-O-L-E, right?
I believe everything's part of this, we're all connected, we're all...
Fake red world
It's a curse. I mean, it's like worse. We're holy or unholy. We're like we're like a lot of things
It's very complicated being a human we're the most complicated
Satanism myth. Yeah more you can say the conception of God is a myth, too. I mean or Jesus is a myth. I mean, it's like
What but our myths when it comes down to a mr. Stories, right the stories
Do they have sometimes a meaning?
Do they have sometimes a deeper meaning, allegory,
another thing that people are trying to get people to notice?
It's because of myth, doesn't mean it's useless.
I mean, the story of Lilith, for example,
is very empowering to a lot of women,
even though it was maybe considered like an evil wish
back in the days, vilified by Judaism.
Now it's kind of taken like this,
Women's live thing and I'm going to I'm going to go over some of my horoscope with you guys because I you know chat
GPT is
Has run it and said some really really interesting things that I've been like
Really thinking a lot about because I have some really interesting placements
for example
In the house of justice
Yeah, mine is well by Libra. Okay, so there's Libra exalted in there, right?
Also Jupiter's in there. Jupiter is exalted. Also, it's that or if he's not exalted
He's twice as powerful there. Also Saturn is exalted there for sure in the sixth house, right?
And then Pluto's there too, which is like the most negative planet, but then I got all the other good stuff happening there
Plus it's about justice, right? Maybe the justice will involve my death or something like that some day. I don't know
I would I would die I would die for justice
But, so that's a six house, three leavers, three leavers.
Also, I got a lot of interesting stuff with it.
I can kind of go through, it's all math and strategy.
You start as small, scale up and out the hang of it.
So, hold on.
Oh, hey Paige, message you on Discord at birdex.
Okay, okay, so you're on kick, okay.
Yeah, I don't I mean, it's like I don't know how much people are making from kick
I'm just streaming here for the first two singles right now. I do tick-tock. I do a not mainly YouTube and
Kick is another one I set up. I basically haven't hardly anybody going there, but I would like to build it up
I see there's a tarot community there. I just don't know how to like I
Would have to just go and watch their programs and like participate and meet people on there
Which I'm not really apt to do because it's not as like
Appealing to me as as kick-talk. It's because I thought a lot of video games
But guys so I'm exciting stuff happening though so once I get this new computer, I think I'm gonna get a computer
I'm thinking maybe hopefully I'll be able to like for around six hundred dollars get a decent one
Okay, I just want to do something decent like I wanted to be able to at least plug in virtual reality
Does anybody know anything about computers that can help me out? I just need to know
If I can get it because I asked chat GPT about it chat GPT is kind of stuck in
2024 or something like that because he's like, oh no, it's way too expensive. He's he's like that's too cheap
You can't put that I was like can I spend like $300 on it because the VR with his mini computers that are out
It was like no no no no no
It was like there's like me is like saying no no no it was saying oh that's you need like a thousand dollar
I was like, I don't know about that. I have my last computer was a thousand dollars
I don't know. I had like five years ago. It ran VR just fine
Hey PG, how are you? I'm sorry guys? I'm having so I think I might return these glasses because these are just like hard to see in
And I forgot one of my other ones. So I'm kind of blind right now. Oh
The smoke is something backer
But again guys, I've actually been able to like get a lot of cool stuff though
I've gotten well now that I clean my apartment
I will be able to bring a lot of cool stuff out that I haven't shared with you yet
I have books.
I have a cult thing.
I mean, I have a lot of great things.
And so I really, hopefully, will be able to get.
OK, so then I'm going to basically
I'm going to get a setup out here.
I'm going to set up maybe to get a new table or something.
I'm going to get set up a computer out here, right here,
OK, and have a little monitor.
and maybe a curved monitor or something,
like a really cool curved monitor or something.
Monitors are not that expensive nowadays.
And I'm gonna set up a sound board.
I'm gonna set up a professional microphone.
I'm gonna set up,
I'm gonna get professional headphones eventually.
I mean, these are just,
I just been getting cheap ones till the time comes, right?
I'm gonna set up different things like power chat.
I mean, I have power chat set up, okay?
Hi, Peggy.
It says it's yeah, I'm gonna it's gonna be really cool, and it's I know I'm gonna be able to I've already talked about okay guys
I'm I have the book outline the book is outlined. It's like gonna be by 500 pages
It's gonna be full of really interesting stuff about the panel verse and my experience and other people's experience and
controls and caution a little
Whole it's gonna have the whole shebang everyone all you guys are gonna be in it right and also the deck too
Like a lot of you guys are gonna be in the deck
I think I'm going to actually like for the deck. I might do the deck first. I might start kick-startering it now
It will I think I want to do a run of a hundred decks
For the first run, okay, that will cost
$1500 I think it's like $15 a deck
Okay, I'm just I'm kind of sharing stuff with you right now. This is thinking out loud
But you know, I probably shouldn't be thinking out loud so much, but I trust you guys
I'm probably gonna do Kickstarter. I'm gonna look into doing a Kickstarter right away. I'm gonna
Have some things like you know, if you're not included in the deck already. I'm probably gonna have a couple
I'm gonna have some merch made for the deck. I'm gonna have a couple
cards
Let's see yeah a couple cards with people on them and stuff like that like I have this big for example like if you know
If Ziggy was to win this is just an example card. Okay, so there's a there's a Ziggy demon now
I don't appreciate you the Ziggy demon do I have the Ziggy demon handy? Let me see
I do think he's in here somewhere. Oh, he might be my tablet though shit
Um, yeah, I don't have this diggy demon hand, but there's a there's one doesn't it made it my you know
I made a demon called Ziggos. Okay, so it's like and it's based on him
And I don't know what he looks like that. I probably got it kind of right. I'm gonna try to bring it up
Well, I'll give I'll make you a car you can be in the deck even if you
He's just knew the Bible so well he did crazy things. Yeah, hold on
He he didn't know the Bible or he was Jewish. Okay, so he had a Torah
I mean the Bible the New Testament's about him, so I don't think like he quite had read that but yeah
I heard about some of the stuff he did like, you know go to Egypt study in mystery schools
He sowed the Yahweh Yahweh vape into his leg for some reason interestingly
Listen Sarah right by the Jewish or Judaism's oil
tradition which is called the tall mood. He's kind of a little bit not looked at
so well. I don't agree with, I think he's kind of slandered in there, but you know
people can have their, he was a Jewish, right? People can have their thoughts
about it. Let's see, okay so I'm gonna look for this picture of Ziggos. I have
them in here I think. I can probably find it here. That's on the wallpaper
Where are you Zegos step forward what happened I?
Thought I saw him in here today, but maybe I was mistaken
Zeman Zegos
Well, I don't remember I put him
Well, you looked at the evil. I might be somewhere else though. I have to look
Where I have have that maybe it's my
Google I don't know. Oh look have I heard about the gospel of Judas? Yeah, it's a very short gospel
Judas was a disciple, he betrayed Jesus of course, he reminds me of a lot of
Arachne, like the spider character, Arachne is a spider, like Arachnophobia is
named after this Greek goddess, she's not a Greek goddess, she was actually a
Lydian, but she was a weaver, you know, it's like a spider's a weaver, she was a
weaver, that's why she got turned into a spider, because she knows how to weave.
And basically she had hubris because, you know, the really great person was a really great goddess was Athena, not, you know,
Arachne, Arachne really thought highly of herself, and she was actually more talented than Athena, but ultimately Athena is the goddess of
Weavey, so she's not going to overshadow the goddess who's like the archetype of perfect Weavey, even if the human being outpaces the archetype.
It's not supposed to do you're the human beings not supposed to the archetype is like the archetype is not it's not called
Arachne is called, you know, it's after the Athena. So I may just explain it, right? It's an interesting theory
Yeah, well, that's but also like Arachne ends up hanging herself
And that's what you just did, you know
He ended up hanging himself because he betrays you just for 30 pieces of silver
It should be like maybe like $300 today or something like that. Maybe maybe less or
You know and why did you do it?
I think probably jealousy, but there's also things like don't
outside the master. I think that's probably, you know, 48 laws of power.
So it may be not the best example, but if you do outshine,
if you outshine masters, like Jesus was a master, he definitely was.
And so, you know, Jesus kind of outshine him, so he
tried to outdo him or something like that. You know, he tried to, he tried to
Ultimately, you're not supposed to betray people because you will have to feel that karma of betrayal, right?
And I think that's just the law of karma is like what you do to other people, you ultimately have to feel yourself.
You have to like... And so that's why I'm very careful not to be cruel to other people because...
Anything I do to others I think will be done to me or I need to I need to I need to understand it in order to know
I shouldn't be doing that, right?
so
anyhow
So yeah guys, I will, I can't wait to get the better computer to you because I will be able to like see actually the screen like this is like not the easiest thing to stream from my tablet.
It's not really. And so I'm gonna be getting probably a nice camera.
Right.
Frickin menorah it just keeps going and going. It's just like it never died
It's like I've used it for five years almost non-stop. It's just going strong. It's fine
You know, it's just doesn't have little difficulties charging sometimes, but it's a good tablet
Yeah, so brown panda
You not like insane, but extraordinary. Yeah. No, I think he was extraordinary. Okay
Okay, so let's see
Take out all this jam is profitable
Yeah, I don't know if you're like, yeah, so I guess you're allowed to do that kind of stuff on kick
Hold on. Okay. It's not it's all math and study for interested message on discord at burn decks zero two
Okay, I'm psyche. I'm psyche awakens. You know, it's like I'm doing like a lot of stuff right now like super like I'm
I'm definitely not probably gonna be stopped promoting any kind of like gambling or anything, but
Would like to maybe know if you have if you have any information about just how to like just start it or if kick it
Can profitable or something. You know, yeah, you can walk me through it. I just you know, I know I just want you to waste waste time
You know, I'm very
Focused on doing my my my book my tarot deck and my my two shows
You see busy people are like, oh, what do you do? Like I'm doing a lot
I've been working harder than I ever have in my entire life doing all this stuff, right?
Even with all the help I'm getting you know, it would be impossible if I didn't have like this, you know, some of this
It's really cool AI helping me with a lot of stuff now. It's fine like AI. I wouldn't have trusted it before
but now it's getting to the point where it is so responsive to like, you know, the desires of the
It's getting so perfected and yeah, you really would be especially if you don't, I mean, I don't have the ability to play a musical instrument like that well, right?
I'm just like, I don't have the patience to learn it. It's like it just wasn't something I learned in my childhood.
So, you know, even I did try to learn piano. I'll never be a great piano player, right? It's just like, I don't have the patience for it.
compose songs, I can write the lyrics, put it to piano music, or I can, like, you know,
have even lyrics, you know, I can put input into it and have these lyrics that have the
exact thing I'm trying to convey, but written in a very good way, like, I don't think I
could.
But also, guys, do you understand how AI works, kind of, like AI is like, it's basically,
It predicts like the next word after the word before so it's like every word is like it's like it's like God is so perfect
It I but it's able to predict exactly what the perfect response would be for some of these things, right?
opera the response I
Just I'll say I'll say his praises. I didn't think it's amazing. I do think it's inch. Yeah, okay
Burn decks zero two. I mean, I'll do that once again
Okay, I sense it, burn dex, okay, burn dex, 0 of 2.
Yes, I got it right, that's enough for every question.
So, we'll talk.
I did find a really cool website called TubeBuddy.
And it is just basically, you know, I think we'll be able to work it better once I get
Guys, I mean, I've always wanted to have the channel like now. I have the channel like the channels good now
I can actually I can like also start to on
Take some stuff off the membership put it on a monetization
I'm actually I can make some decent money just from the views now. I'm getting good views. I'm getting good retention
I'm getting
So I'm able to, you know, I do appreciate, you know, guys, if you do run like some of the old episodes
So just when you sleep and the stuff over as you run, you know, that'd be awesome
I
Got I get creative sometimes, you know, also guys, I do a offering a few readings
I know it's a little bit. It's kind of quiet tonight. I guess nobody wanted to come hang out with me
You know, I guess maybe I'm boring people. Maybe people don't like me anymore. I don't know, but I want to thank you guys
I love you guys
Guys things are just gonna get better. Okay, maybe we're going through some rough times occasionally. Okay, but
Hi Darryl morning, I bet beta is full of regrets this morning after yesterday's performance
I hope she's what happened with beta. I
Think you was fine yesterday. I mean I mean guys. I have a chocolate mousse cheesecake right now
I'm gonna eat half of it. I think I'm really hungry
Earlier I had a macaroni and cheese and I have this frozen cheese cake from the cheese cake factory chocolate mousse cheesecake
It is frozen, I don't know
My chocolate I have not even opened I can't believe I have not opened this in like months
So I hang out with you guys for I just can't it's like I can't see that. Well, I wish I could
read
Screen easier
So it's really sad my neighbor actually moved out my next door neighbor
They have the beautiful dog. I love and
There's awesome people, but she got pregnant
Wow guys, look at this. This looks so awesome
Cheesecake gets some Doritos later
Maybe I'm gonna put this on a plate. Hold on. Oh
I have a plate for this. I'll cut off it. Oh
At least let me give it a go knife out. Hold on
Mm-hmm
Grabbing a knife, okay
Yeah, I don't mean to get down on myself, you know, I just don't know why I
Don't know why
Sometimes I do good here sometimes I don't do that good. Hey axe. Hey was up. So what happened with Vita though?
Can you explain something she had a massive argument with Jim Nick? Oh, yeah, I saw
I mean, I did see that but I think then I saw on Kate's like I think I don't know if she was on Kate's
But she seemed like she made up with her
So I don't know
Wow, so this is kind of frosted over his cake, okay
I need to like let it start out for a while
Yeah, I heard that she was fighting with Jim Nicky tonight, but honestly
It's like I
Think sometimes she just has bad, you know
You get some bad moves and also sometimes being on a show
You can sometimes you know, you know change your personality
Based on different factors. Well, this is good. I
Don't think that she's like a bat like mean or bad or anything
I think that sometimes she like expects a lot of people from a lot of people. I don't want to talk about it
Oh
Trying to cut this kid this frozen up. Oh cheesecake is so thick
Mmm
So fast over
It's good
It's edible
Very tasty
Very rich
It's a good mess like
Like too sweet. Mm-hmm. Hey, Loa. Okay. Hey, Tricks. Come on
You're sweet
Okay, you're on PC. I was it's tasty
It's kind of soft it's like, you know, it's a second you like the golden girls you do that
I'll finish that off in a few days. Yeah, I got shakes. Come on shakes. I give you
Hey, babe, the cats out. There's Lola come on Lola
Cats are all doing good
That is very good
Hey, I hope she's not you know, you know
Yes, they're very very sweet person. She doesn't have a good heart. She gets
We all have
We go through moves, right?
And I may I've not been the perfect friend. I you know, I've made mistakes. I
Can understand why she's been upset with me sometimes that I've been sometimes upset with her. Oh, but you know what?
When you're friends and you're true friends, you can like, you know forgive people. I
hope she's forgiven me
It's like I love to let you buy guns be by guns. I like your orange and relatable
Unreliable your religion untrackable anyway
Not sure if 19 people in chat. Okay. We're growing
Yeah, so it's kind of cool on a on tiktok though. I don't know if you guys are familiar with tiktok
well first of all tiktok is weird because
Last night I got put on restricted like twice or almost. Yeah twice other nights. It happens
At least one time it's interesting that the people who love replying that Jesus hung out with prostitutes rejected the religious are the very people who usually themselves rejected Jesus or
any talk of him isn't that right shoes?
captain of a starship because
They'll say that I mean it's a it seems they a lot of people that are
You know into Christianity don't don't like Jesus
and even like
You know, what's his name? ESA like I said they like uses right and then it's like these the Jesuits
It said it makes it it says
ISH it's like it's trying to say shit. Okay, it's like it's a pretty image shit
Okay, that's what it did. They're not fans of him. They're they're Catholic. They're like Mary and stuff, right?
You're not really done trackable
You didn't make me. Oh, what are you talking about being a bit of make anybody since you make you because I saw I saw
Or the Joker make you I saw you on Joker's version before anybody. You didn't make me
You know what we all we all are making ourselves, you know be to help me so much
I think I felt beat it to I just beat it a page and different people
I mean it's like we both have our you know our people that we've met and that we've introduced other people
I like to I don't like it's not about like a contest about oh
But it's like not I say she made me you know
I was just so I'm just like some piece of dumb clay that is just like you know
And with nothing until she came along worked your magic now
I'm nothing again because you know a matter of favor for a day or two, right? It's kind of dumb
That was fighting where you don't like it. You don't like a track of what light says on UN. Are you in the United Nations?
Anyway, clumsy, you know, it's like what why do you you know, you always are trying to get like, you know
I'm kind of controversy like how are you just find out how can we just be friends and you have to like
Predator and people against each other. That's one of the things like a lot of the trolls do. Oh
The sort of like shake up all this jealousy that's not even there and like all this anger or something like that is like
You came from good times and I'll be at least you're honest
Well, okay, so good times in all these those are both assholes. I mean
So all these just porn bombing again. Good times. It's just ridiculous. He's just you know, try to hit on
Cage and every other woman on YouTube. I'm not crying
You're just fucking annoying
Go to cure shaved eyebrow, you know broom
But away away from me. I don't know why you fucking you're crying. You're like you're coming you come here bothering me
I don't I don't go looking for you to bother you. You come here harassing me. Oh
Be the major Peter they do
No, she didn't okay my mother my father made me you know 44 years ago. I'm very unique individual
No, no one makes anybody
Except you're making me irritated. That's all you're doing
We'll fight I'll fight. I don't care
Yeah, he's all the army and I'll be just a troll. I mean, it's just a troll army and I fucking I kicked out of all these
Discord, he's the most strict person on discord. He's for all his porn bombing everything
I get kicked out of this court for mentioning that I have a YouTube show
I mean it kind of just how insecure and dumb can you be?
No mention their show no mention their show. I'm saying here. I'll mention everybody show
I subscribe to you being gang you have like a hundred subscribers. I remember looking yesterday
So it's like yeah, I subscribe to people that are like actual content creators and
All the guy kicked off of YouTube
I'm not gonna get him take in my show taken down for all day or sick or anybody else dumb ass that got kicked off of YouTube
Yeah
Yeah, it was he's not there, but yeah, it's like I have all these people like you know
Who's who had these people so mr. Big Pies who had like nobody in his chat ever and then we have the go
Then Aldi Q Q has a little show
But you know Aldi and that Aldi's gotten other people's shows taking down
Because he can't stand people being on YouTube because he can't be on YouTube
I don't know if he has the IP block or something
It seemed like an easy fix just let's have another account, but you know these people are so bad
They're actually kicked off of YouTube. Are you ever heard of this?
They're actually kicked off of YouTube. They're like YouTube is like get the fuck up. We know we're near here
I don't know how they're allowed to go on panels. I'm afraid I'm gonna put them on panels. They
They're saying horrible things
They say I'm lucky enough that I'm able to shut it down and turn it off in time
But it's like they've said some things that I say I'm just so lucky. I'm like, I'm very lucky that the show's still around
It has to be an angel or something like watching out for the show for me to still be around
Hey, you're just not hearing from anything. Just wanted to share what's worked for you. Okay. Okay. Um, I'm
Bella's like, I don't know if okay. I did I I
Friended you on discord. No, you don't you know
You're saying the exact same thing though. I don't know if this is like some kind of like a
AI like repeating itself or something
But I'll talk to you, I'll talk to you.
I don't know if you heard, but I'll talk to you.
What are your thoughts on the queue and hot pockets break up?
Well, wasn't he just like kind of using hot pockets?
I mean, it's like, I mean, she was like, you know,
he was making fun of me and stuff,
like saying horrible things about me.
I don't know what Q's problem is.
Baby cheeky checking all BD.
Hold on, I have to check it this first time.
No, no, no, no, no.
What if people, people are accusing me of all kinds of things? Oh, you're on this, you're on that. You have HIV. You're, you know,
hitting on guys. Everyone has problems.
That's why it's like, it's not even fun sometimes to be on YouTube with these trolls. I'm just saying the same shit over and over again.
It's like, oh, it's just like, it's getting old. It's like not creative. It's just mean. It's dumb.
I'm not like, I was hacking any of you.
I'm just fucking reacting to how I'm basically treated sometimes by these trolls, but I shouldn't expect good treatment, but
You know what? I give the trolls relevance. They don't give me relevance
Trolls brought nothing really to my show except trouble
I've given them a platform new life
Well, you didn't baby cheeky, but that's what people are saying like other people were saying that yesterday
I don't know who you are or like how you know me
You just I've never seen you before you just show up in the middle of the night like you know me
Then you bring 40 people in acts and you bring 40 people into the chat where'd you bring these people you brought some people here
Thank you acts. I appreciate you
It's okay. It's like I do like if like people are participating at least even if they don't like me
But I just don't like
When people that are cut like ours, you know, just come here to get attention for themselves and then they're like in the root to me
Like the whole thing. I'm trying to help people get attention for themselves. I
Don't know. I'm trying to really help
People, you know, if you want you guys want advice, I'm giving advice to people on tiktok and and YouTube about a lot of stuff
And I say if I don't know the answer I can get to the end. I mean, it's like I
Figured out a lot of stuff. I'm basically I've been through the whole
I know the YouTube stuff like the back of my hand now. I'm going to go back and
Start doing putting tags with all my videos changing some of the tiles with thumbnails
Bringing back some of the episodes maybe editing some of the old ones when I get my computer
That'll be it. I'll be able to fly through that. It'll just
Guys, it'll be such a cool channel. There'll be said there'll be good classic episodes. We can have reruns and stuff
I know some people like reruns as
Yeah
Yeah, well a little bit maybe good, you know, I know I'm not a big fan of commercials not a big fan of reruns
But sometimes I haven't seen the rerun that I like them, right?
There's a lot of people that haven't seen watching me for some time
You have no business giving other people advice when you don't even take others or even yours
Guys and Jamie Jamie, can you take can you take that person off and?
Yeah, just that person maybe cheeky you can watch me for some time. Well, you don't think criticize me
I do think people's advice that you understand I get told so much bullshit. I don't feel like listening to it
I'm gonna do what I want to do. Okay
my show my show like that's a good thing about like actually being successful and like actually like
You know building something yourself from the ground up, you know on this platform and being successful
Which I am and I'm successful on YouTube. I'm making for four figures, you know
On YouTube, which a lot of people aren't doing
Even monetized people aren't doing okay. It's not easy. I
Spend a lot of time a lot of time
Energy and a lot of people have to a lot of people who've been supporting the show loving the show. Okay. This is a good show
this show does help people too and
Sometimes people
Yeah, so you're right. Sometimes people are
You know don't take their own advice
But sometimes they know the advice to give though, you know, sometimes they should be listened to
Okay, so I'm going to create an AI picture. Can I say a
troll
Drooling
A fat troll drooling on their keyboard
with a dumb look on their face, with a dumb expression.
That's just what I picture when I think
of some of these people.
That troll me, okay?
I'm gonna do a starry night.
Let's see if it makes it.
My image cannot be created, just try something else, okay?
I'll just say troll. I won't say fat. Okay, so troll with a
Dole expression with a dole
With a dole, okay
Suggested okay, I cannot be created shit
I'll say a monster a monster. I'm not a monster
Make it more open-ended. I don't know if this AI is not impressing me this uh,
Microsoft's I guess it is. Come on.
Impress me. Okay, it's making it. Finally.
Creating the image guys. We have it coming up. You couldn't make a troll, but it can make a monster for some reason. We'll see.
We'll see how it does it.
Hey, Axe. This is an AI. Okay, so it says, oh, okay. It says monster zooling on their keyboard with adult expression is in the suggested style. Okay.
Well
I mean it's not good it's not perfect, but it's interesting. I mean the AI did not understand obviously
It's I mean it's like I meant like typing at the computer not like sitting on a literal keyboard. Okay
It's just a troll probably is what that person
Bean gang or
whatever that a
Whatever their name was baby cheeky. That's what that's baby cheeky and bean gang. That's they look like right now
There's little monsters little tiny monsters today on the keyboard thinking ah, I'm the king in the world
There's like these little monsters
Hey Slayer
So there you go. I'll save that image pretty cool
Okay, if I mean I apologize for people are mean to me sometimes I I don't think I deserve it quite
Have to be so mean so I
am
Try to do my best, okay, and do it my best with what I got
I'm no I'm no
I'm not an I'm not an angel, but I'm not a demon either. I might be related to the devil, but
We're just cousins or something, okay
You like a little monster hi
So I haven't I just think it makes a mandala. Let me see if I can make it so I can here's a mandala templates
Yeah, mandala's are very calming to do so. I think I was like
So I see this this is this I think this is the shrie. That's the shrie on show. That's the triangle
Let me see if they have it or they have actually a
Flower of life. I'll do that one. So that's a flower of life
Okay, so he has all connected and we are all connected in this flower of life anything that is
it also looks like eyes let me see what I can do with it I'll make these pink
hold on how we do it they drop it drop it like it huh okay oh you have to do
kind of exact there we go
you can go across I'm just gonna do all the little things in pink
And then I'll do the other stuff in green all like the little star things we pink
These are all coming together, right?
It is interesting how things are connected and when you do things like this you kind of realize that everything's all in this one
Mandala the whole the whole world is right
Actually in Buddhism
The mandala is actually like this actual astral place. Okay. Let's go back home astral place where it's like they
invoke these deities and demons and guardians into it,
they'll have very elaborate meditations
where they're going through these mandalas
and they make it out of sand, right?
And then they, at the end of the retreat,
they just dissolve it and they just mess up
all the colored sand and it turns back into the...
Turns just back into the earth, right? And that's that's that's how the universe works to it. It's a constant destruction and recreation
Okay, so in the back. Okay, there we go
So I think this is looking pretty cool so far, you know
Got this see how it's all like weaving together. I'm like weaving this right now, right?
You do I'm gonna do so this is I'm gonna do all these shapes in the same shape. Oops everything. That's like
This little Vesca Pisces and that's the shape of our eyes the best of Pisces
Also the fish are kind of like our eyeballs, right?
Our fish are kind of our eyes are kind of like fish
Because they always have to be in in a moisture, right? They are they're they
They have pupils and no fish go in schools. I don't know. I'm just making things up now. Okay
I'm almost done with the
This part of it now look what I got so far. Okay, so I think it's all done
Okay
Yeah
There we go. So I've done that
Completed that part of it now. I have to do some other parts of it
So I think we use this big beautiful blue and I'll just like do the rest of it in this blue
It would be very exact. Okay, so like that
And I kind of reminds me of these pink and blue is like, you know, that's a color of like
You know when people are welcoming babies or something they have this you know, it's either boy or girl the pink and blue kind of like life
Is like we our parents are all weavers of our DNA
strands brought us to this world
And we have this unique expression that is the combination of both them
It's the alchemy of both of our parents right hopefully the best best parts of them
But we'll take on some of their negative qualities too, you know, and there's generational curses and there's also
Oops, there's difference that there's just different stuff, right? There's shit. Oh, let's go back a little bit. Yeah, there's different
Right here
there's different things that we go through and different lessons we have to learn and stuff but
Once we learn the lesson, I don't think we have to repeat them, and I think that I've
learned a lot of lessons.
I had to make a lot of mistakes like several times, you know, more than one time, more
than twice, more than two, three, four, five, maybe I made mistakes hundreds of times, right?
Ultimately, will you learn from the mistakes, right?
That's what you really hope.
I'm not trying to do, okay, so I finished it.
Is that pretty?
Karmic friends, right? You always see people as little fish
Yeah, I mean people are and people I mean we are kind of like we started esteem like a seaman, right?
But that's part that's part of our DNA is like carried by the seaman, right?
It's like a little tadpole basically looks just like a tadpole and what happens to the tadpole it starts to transform
I think in once we're in the
Once we're in the room we go from a tadpole to a
for frog to like a little monkey to
Amphibians and you all kinds of stuff and yeah, and we're also in like this water state
You know it's like when we're in our mother we're in like the water, right?
And so that's when our mother gives birth like you know, it's all like ships
Like go into birth or they go I know they go to dock and there's the doctor, right the dock
I don't know it's a so the pregnancy and the maritime stuff is all related because the
the babies are under this maritime because they're they're not born and so that's why I guess the
A, B, or T, I, O, N is kind of controversial. I don't know. I just like to think about weird stuff like that.
So guys, if you would like to schedule a
private reading, I'll do it over the phone,
or on Discord, I can do it through video,
or I can even create you a YouTube video,
or do a private live with you or something like that.
We'll just give you the link,
and then you can go on,
and you can just do a normal chat on YouTube.
I will get for members. I will give like another 33 percent time
So it's like a bit so it's for half hour. It's like a half hour normal to which is like 25 bucks
I'll do 45 minutes for 25 bucks for members for members
That's a pretty good deal. So if you do become a member and you you know, you could actually like get like 20
That 25 minutes basically for free, right that extra, you know for five bucks pretty good deal. So I should buy bucks, but
I know that a lot of people come here for stuff
other than the tarot, and I appreciate those people, too.
I appreciate all you guys.
But I would like to get more active in doing readings.
I do like doing my kicking off the panel and stuff like that.
That's all fun and good and well and stuff like that.
But it's like, we go through different phases, you know?
We had some difficult times lately. We know what happened to you know, our friend Michael passed away
You know, and it's like and some people weren't very nice to him and yeah
Did I you know kick him off the panel sometime and stuff like that? Yeah, I did and he was you know
controversial, but I feel kind of bad. I kicked him off, you know sometimes
That was it, but he always took it in stride and he was always a good sport about it
But I do when I like, you know
Always what I just don't like though like the last memory. Hopefully it's the last memory of me is not just like kicking off the panel
It's like I just don't know what happened to him and it's like it's you know
He died so young and stuff like that is seems like I don't know
I hope hopefully nothing didn't do anything to himself or anything. I got really hope he did not
I guess why I'm trying to get Merna here to explain
What happened if she will
Personalize the videos down interesting. Yeah, so if you'd like I mean, I'll do if you want to do the
The video chat like you know, he's we just do it on discord. There's a video there
Or I'll make you a personalized video and I I'll do it like you know
I'll just do 30 minutes of just recording it and I'll send you the video
I'll post it on YouTube give you the link and private link
I think 25 dollars very reasonable very reasonable and I'm really surprised that people are really taking advantage of it and
because
I think it's a good good value and you will I can also satisfaction guaranteed if you're not happy with your reading
I'll refund you okay
He doesn't remember you at the moment nine percent sure of it
You know he didn't know he didn't like thinking that that's the last moment. It's the last you know
He didn't think of that of course, but
I wonder if like that's like one of his like final thoughts of me. Was that happening because that doesn't happen
Oh, look at this. This is really cool. So you ever notice a fractal. It looks kind of like Buddha
You see that they look kind of like Buddha like a little tin man or something and then it goes in it goes forever though
You know, you keep like you like go closer not a fractal works
You go you go to the tip of it and you can go keep going further and further in right so we're going through in there, right?
Now we can go to like the tip of that and it's gonna be like a whole other like a universe
So you see if they need to go on forever. I mean, it's not very best example, but
It's a pinch to zoom I
That's pretty cool
Now I'm way in okay, then you can zoom out
Let's see how I do that
Pinch to zoom. Oh, no Henry said it. How do we set it?
Well, I messed it up. Okay, but oh, here's what it was cool. I'll play this for a minute. This will I did buy the
violet color the ultraviolet the
Violet flame is in this Tibetan bell thing. Oh, yeah, I just found this it's been bowls and it sounds so pretty
Here we go. Oh
I guess I didn't buy it. Okay. No, thanks. Okay, so
Okay, that was that. That was the heart.
You can imagine these chakras pulsating inside of you while you're hearing these tones.
The tones go along with it. The body is like a musical instrument in a way.
I may not say the piano, but I play the body.
And I'll do... How about the... Finally, we'll do...
Oh, we can do full full like there's a chakra right there. It's a green chakra. This is beautiful. Actually, I really really enjoy in this that is the Tibetan symbols
Which are similar to the Sanskrit
Pretty huh
Beautiful. I don't know if I'm allowed to play the music. So anyway, I
Just wanted to come on tonight and say I love you guys and thank you for sticking by me
I know that it's like we've been through some ups downs good bad, you know controversy whatever
Sadness happiness. We've been through it all. It's like, you know, it's a show
But I do I do what do you want to thank you and even if like, you know, I don't know
It's like my the audience has given up on me here. I think I have been slandered pretty bad where it's like, you know
People will just they say whole things like people don't say shit other people like they say I don't see other people get called
The names I get called and maybe that's just my cross to bear, right? And it's like yeah, I don't fight
I don't think I deserve it, but
I'll uh, I accept my fate whatever it is. I believe in this thing called a more fahti
Which means lover of fate like I love whatever happens. I it's my life and uh, I
Accept my fate. I love my fate
Um guys, if you would like to book the reading, okay, I
Would love to help some people out. I do have some time this week and
I
Promise you'll let you like it, but I'll let you guys go and have a good night. I'll see you later
Sleep well sweet dreams
Don't let the bed bugs bite